<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ledge Partners</title><description></description><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com</link><atom:link
    href="https://www.ledgepartners.com/feed.rss"
    rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"
/><language>en</language><generator>Ignite v0.6.0</generator><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/careers-text</guid><title>Our Criteria</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/careers-text</link><description><![CDATA[We are always on the lookout for undergraduate or graduate students interested in joining our team on a part-time or full-time basis. While we cannot offer paid internships at this time, we can offer you opportunities to learn about small business acquisitions and gain mentorship in the fields of investment banking, consulting and startups through an unpaid internship. You’ll spend your time searching for acquisition opportunities and helping us with operational and financial diligence of small businesses. If you are interested, reach out below and we’d love to chat!]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[careers]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/aboutUs</guid><title>About Us</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/aboutUs</link><description><![CDATA[Justin Purnell is a seasoned business leader with over 20 years of experience in product management, strategy, and operations, renowned for his integrity and commitment to transparency. With a proven track record of driving growth and innovation, Justin combines analytical rigor with a user-centric approach to create effective solutions. His strong focus on culture ensures that the values and legacy of businesses are honored and preserved. Known for his flexibility, he tailors strategies to meet individual needs, fostering sustainable growth and a positive work environment. Justin’s exceptional management skills and dedication make him the ideal steward for businesses ready to embark on their next chapter.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[about us]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/philosophy-text</guid><title>Our Philosophy</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/philosophy-text</link><description><![CDATA[Regardless of industry or size, we manage any operation according to five principles: 1) integrity, 2) long-term focus, 3) culture, 4) flexibility, and 5) management quality. We are committed to sustainable success through ethical stewardship and respectful collaboration.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[values]]></category><category><![CDATA[philosophy]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/valueProposition</guid><title>Our Value Proposition</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/valueProposition</link><description><![CDATA[IntegrityAs a business leader, Ledge Partners prioritizes integrity above all else. When you consider selling your business, you want a buyer who will be transparent and honest throughout the process. Our commitment to ethical practices ensures that you will receive a fair valuation, open communication, and respect for the legacy you’ve built. We understand that your business is not just an asset; it’s your life’s work. By choosing to sell to Ledge Partners, you’re partnering with a team that will honor your values and maintain the trust you’ve established with your employees and customers.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[value proposition]]></category><category><![CDATA[valueProposition]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/criteria-text</guid><title>Our Criteria</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/criteria-text</link><description><![CDATA[At Ledge Partners, we specialize in acquiring businesses that fit our carefully curated investment criteria. Our mission is to partner with exceptional companies, ensuring a seamless transition while fostering growth and sustainability.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[criteria]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ledgepartners.com/contact-us-text</guid><title>Our Criteria</title><link>https://www.ledgepartners.com/contact-us-text</link><description><![CDATA[Interested? Get in touch]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ledge Partners]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[ledge partners]]></category><category><![CDATA[contact us]]></category></item></channel></rss>